Guide to the Andrew Dickson White papers, 1832-1919.
White, Andrew Dickson papers, 1832-1919
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Horace White, June 10, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Otis Bigelow, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - George Bliss, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Skull & Crossbones, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Mary G. Hart, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - J.C. Hendrix, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - K. T., June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - W.J. Youmans, June 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - C.K. Adams, June 12, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - William Preston Johnston, June 12, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, June 12, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - J.C. Stookly, June 12, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Perry Allen, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Perry Allen, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Joseph Bruckner, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Julius D. Dreher, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - John W. Hoyt, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Everett Wheeler, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - George Russell Young, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Adams, June 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - George Lincoln Burr, June 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Frederick White, June 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Perry Allen, June 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - D. Appleton & Co., June 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - E.C. Cleaves, June 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter to the board of trustees of Cornell University
  - A.O. Faith, June 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - W.L. Dening, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - W.L. Dening, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - E.R. Maxson, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - W.J. Quinlan, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - S.J. Russel, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Letter. Letter to the Board of Trustees of Cornell University
  - Frederick White, June 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Perry Allen, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Earl Barnes, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - D.J. Brewer, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - E.S. Plumb, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - M. S., June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Frederick White, June 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Perry Allen, June 18, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Bruce, June 18, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Perry Allen, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Edward G. Allen, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - E.M. Bouldin, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Charles S. Francis, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Mary Dana Hicks, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - A.R. Spofford, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Yale Commencement, June 19, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Mary M. Adams, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Edward G. Allen, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Mark Bigelow, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - John W. Hoyt, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - R.U. Johnson, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - John Nordhouse, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - E.S. Plumb, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - K. T., June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    Letter. Addressed to George Lincoln Burr; five pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 20, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Gertrude Walker-Egbert, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - George Bliss, June 21, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Edward L. Nichols, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - M. M., June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - E.S. Plumb, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - George Putnam, June 22, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Perry Allen, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Perry Allen, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - W.E. Greenswalt, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - M. Fluegel, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Frederick William Holls, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Professor Burr, letter from Justin Winsor
  - Hernry B. Lord, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - A.O. Faith, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Frederick White, June 23, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - J. Brusche, June 24, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, June 24, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - James Burrill Angell, June 24, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Undescribed, June 24, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Monsalvat School (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Prospectus.
  - Franklin Spencer Edmonds, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Gertrude Walker-Egbert, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from F.B. Sanborn
  - F.B. Sanborn, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - William H. Short, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to Frederick William Holls; three pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Frederick White, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Horace White, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - James M. Whiton, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - William j. Young, June 25, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Frederick William Holls, June 26, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Mary Bigelow, June 26, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, June 26, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Perry Allen, June 26, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - E.S. Plumb, June 26, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Perry Allen, June 27, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - John W. Hoyt, June 27, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Clara White Newberry, June 27, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - E.S. Plumb, June 27, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - James M. Whiton, June 27, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Justin Winsor, June 28, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - S. Holmes, June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Pope Manuacturing Co., June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Henry Wade R., June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - W. S., June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Goldwin Smith, June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Frederick White, June 29, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Theodore Bacon, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Samuel A. Green, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Frederick William Holls, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Juliet J.P. Hill; two pages
  - Frederick White, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Justin Winsor, June 30, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - C.K., June 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Frederick William Frost, June 1896 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Perry Allen, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - D. Appleton & Co., July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Charles S. Francis, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - John W. Hoyt, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Jenkin Lloyd Jones, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Charles A. Watts, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Frederick White, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - W.J. Youmans, July 1, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Charles S. Francis, July 2, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - E.S. Plumb, July 2, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Ruth Putnam, July 2, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Horace White, July 2, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Horace White, July 2, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - C.F. Adams, July 3, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - D. Appleton & Co., July 3, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - F.B. Sanborn, July 5, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 3, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - A.O. Faith, July 3, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - William McKinley, July 4, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Mary E.B. Whiton, July 4, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - George Lincoln Burr, July 5, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - C.K. Adams, July 5, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - George Lincoln Burr, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Julius D. Dreher, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - J.G. Schurman, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Goldwin Smith, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Stewart L. Woodford, July 6, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - D. Appleton & Co., July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - David J. Brewer, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Undescribed, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Goldwin Smith, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 7, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    Letter. Addresed to D.J. Hill
  - Arthur W., July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - William P. Robinson, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to Goldwin Smith
  - Frederick White, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Frederick White, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Yorke-Powell, July 8, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 9, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - A.O. Faith, July 9, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 10, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Goldwin Smith, July 10, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 10, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to D. Appleton & Co.
  - David J. Hill, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - William H. Sage, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Horace White, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Stewart L. Woodford, July 11, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Edward L. Pierce, July 12, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Clara White Newberry, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - The Rochester Herald, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Newspaper Article. Two pages
  - Frederick White, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Frederick White, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - E.S. Williams, July 13, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Comfork, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Frederick William Holls, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Severo Mallett-Prevost, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - W.H. Pope, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - A.T. Waterman, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Letter. Fifteen pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Letter. Addressed to David J. Hill; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Ruth Mary White, July 14, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Frederick William Holls, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Frederick William Holls, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Edward F. Jones, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Clara White Newberry, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Emilie, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Fort Ontario, July 15, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    Invitation. Centennial celebration
  - Walter H. Page, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Ellis A. Apgar, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - H.L. Atchison, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Theodore Bacon, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - G.N. Crosby, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Charles E. Fitch, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Charles E. Fitch, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Theodore B. Foster, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Lester Franklin, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - J.B. Hargrave, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - J.C. Hendrix, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Archibald Hopkins, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Eastman, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - A. Keet, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - George K. Knapp, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - J.J. McCabe, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - J.M. Mays, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Undescribed, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - The New York Press, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Tribune, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Walter H. Page, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - E.S. Plumb, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Potter, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Daniel S. Remsen, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Abrahm S. Hewitt
  - William P. Robinson, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Charles E. Sanborn, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - F.L. Union, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Albert M., July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - F. W., July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Frederick White, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Horace K. White, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Ruth Mary White, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - James M. Whiton, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - George W. Williams, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - J.A. Williams, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - W.L. W., July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - George Russell Young, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Undescribed, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - The Troy Daily times, July 16, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - C.K. Adams, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - The Advertiser, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Bayne, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - John A. Cass, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Comfork, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - H.W. Dunlap, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Sunday World-Herald, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - George B. Kline, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Clara White Newberry, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - The Rochester Herald, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - John R. Smith, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - R.J. T., July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Clifford C. Whitman, July 17, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Edward G. Allen, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Perry Allen, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - B.O. Duncan, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Ernest G. Gould, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Charles Houghton, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - S.C. Kelsey, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Redford Sharpe, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse Journal, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - H.L. Wayland, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - U.G. Weatherly, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Clifford Whitmore, July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - H. H., July 18, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - George Lincoln Burr, July 19, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 19, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Frederick D. White, July 19, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Ruth Mary White, July 19, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Everett V. Abbot, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Everett V. Abbot, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - J. Edwards Clarke, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - The Cleveland Recorder, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - John W. Dwight, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - A. Gaylord, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - S.T. Golding, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Frederick William Holls, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - George W. Jones, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - George K. Knapp, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Frederick D. White, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Alfred Williams, July 20, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Charles Babcock, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Gilman, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Seabury S. Gould, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Frederick White
  - A.E. Keet, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Sara White Lee, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Letter. Two pages; enclosed: newspaper article
  - Pepper, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - William H. Sage, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - John DeWitt Warner, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - A.H. Sashburn, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Frederick White, July 21, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth E. Evans, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - E.A. Merritt, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - J. O'Donnell, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - George E. Priest, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - J.H. Senter, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - T. Guilford Smith, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Undescribed, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - C.W.E. Snyder, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. George L. Stearns, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Letter. Addressed to Pres. D.J. Hill; two pages
  - Stewart L. Woodford, July 22, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Everett V. Abbot, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - C.K. Adams, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - A.W. Bishop, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - James Bryce, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - S.S. Gould, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Archibald Hopkins, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Poem.
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - H.A. Richmond, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - M.R. Wise, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Stewart L. Woodford, July 23, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Henry I. Bliss, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Obituary.
  - Edward C. Dixon, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - E.P. Evans, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - J.C. Hendrix, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Frederick William Holls, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - W.P. W., July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - A.E. Keet, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - J.P. O'Toole, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Frank P. Ryan, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Horace White, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Letter. Two pages; White's nephew
  - Frederick White, July 24, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - The American, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - E.P. Evans, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - James J. Storrow, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Charles Morris Smith, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Charles R. K., July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - A.B. Stone, July 25, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Lester F. Ward, July 26, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Mary D., July 26, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Charles Warner, July 26, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - James Hillhouse Alexander, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - C., July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - A.V. Hoyt, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - John W. Irwin, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - C.R. Sherwood, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Alfred Williams, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Clifford Whitmore, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Frederick White, July 27, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Montreal Daily Herald, July 28, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 28, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    Letter. Addressed to Mrs. Hill
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 28, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - D. Appleton & Co., July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - George Lincoln Burr, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - David J. Hill, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - R.G.H. Speed, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Oscar S. Straus, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Frederick White, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - C.K. Adams, July 29, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Cornelius Baldwin, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - George P. Fisher, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Undescribed, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - George L. Stearns, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - William C. Wallace, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Alling, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Alling, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Undescribed, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - D. Appleton & Co., July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - James F. Gluck, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - P. O., July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 31, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Undescribed, July 30, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Undescribed, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - F. Harrison, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Herman Schoenfeld, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - John DeWitt Warner, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, August 1, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - George L. Burr, August 2, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - D. Appleton & Co., August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Daisy M. George, August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Rafael Navarro, August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    Letter. Enclosed: newspaper article
  - Clara White Newberry, August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Edwin F. Northrup, August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Charles Tucker, August 3, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - G.W. Agee, August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - G.W. Agee, August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - E., August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Henry J. White, August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - F. Yorke-Powell, August 4, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Frederick William Holls, August 5, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Beatrice Magill, August 5, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - John Smallwood, August 5, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    Letter. Enclosure
  - Andrew Strong White, August 5, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - D. Appleton & Co., August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - David J. Brewer, August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Edward C. Dixon, August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - S.T. Golding, August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - E. Huffert, August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - A.E. Keet, August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - E.D. M., August 6, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - George K. Knapp, August 7, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, August 7, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Strong White, August 7, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Ruth Mary White, August 7, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, August 8, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, August 8, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - W.W. Rowlee, August 8, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 8, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 8, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    Letter. Addressed to Pres. D.J. Hill
  - Clarence H. Lee, August 9, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Undescribed, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - A.E. Keet, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from F.R. Goudert
  - Charles Marseilles, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - The Union League Club, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - William J. Warrener, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 10, 1896 (Box 76, Folder 10)